{
    "subject": "Antonio_Vega",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Jessica_Buchanan",
    "human_readable": "Antonio Vega is married to Jessica Buchanan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9859768152236938,
            "question": "Is Antonio Vega's wife named Jessica Buchanan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9191082119941711,
            "question": "Are Antonio Vega and Jessica Buchanan in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9057920575141907,
            "question": "To whom is Antonio Vega married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8991017937660217,
            "question": "Is Antonio Vega married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8974222540855408,
            "question": "Who is Antonio Vega married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7161781787872314,
            "question": "Does Jessica Buchanan have a husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6752438545227051,
            "question": "What is the name of Antonio Vega's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6247445940971375,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Antonio Vega?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5782724618911743,
            "question": "What is the name of Jessica Buchanan's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5510402917861938,
            "question": "Who is Jessica Buchanan?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Antonio Vega is married to Jessica Buchanan.",
            "html": "yago_30795_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Jessica Buchanan's husband?",
            "html": "yago_30795_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the marital status of Antonio Vega?",
            "html": "yago_30795_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Antonio Vega's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_30795_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30795_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30795_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30795_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30795_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30795_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30795_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30795_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30795_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30795_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30795_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the documents, I found that:\n\n* Antonio Vega is mentioned as having a romantic relationship with Jessica Buchanan (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_30795/re-ranker-msmarco/68.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_30795/re-ranker-msmarco/57.txt)\n* Jessica Buchanan is mentioned as being married to Antonio Vega (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_30795/re-ranker-msmarco/69.txt)\n\nTherefore, the information in the documents supports the triple.\n\nResponse:\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Antonio Vega is married to Jessica Buchanan. Multiple documents mention their marriage, including `10.txt` and `69.txt`."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}